<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/collections/sugar-syrups.atom"/>
  <title>OnlineOrganics</title>
  <updated>2021-07-23T20:45:24-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>OnlineOrganics</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6864851468449</id>
    <published>2021-07-23T20:45:24-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-07-23T20:45:24-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-yacon-powder"/>
    <title>Organic Yacon Powder (Natural Sweetener)</title>
    <s:type>Powders</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-yacon-powder-pile.png?v=1626549784"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Powders<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            167.70
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic yacon powder is a super sweetener with powerful health benefits. When extracted and used in powdered form, yacon root is a low glycemic natural sweetener, meaning it doesn’t cause a spike in blood sugar. Yacon has some slightly sweet, resinous, and floral (similar to violet) undertones.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is Yacon?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Yacon is a perennial root vegetable that looks something like a sweet potato. Yacon root grows naturally in South America and is known for being both sweet and filling.</li>
<li>Yacon root contains good carbohydrates known as fructoogliosaccharides (FOS). FOS are insoluble fibers or prebiotics that our bodies can’t digest. That might sound like a bad thing, but it’s actually the reason they’re so good for us. They make us feel full without adding calories.</li>
</ul>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>1 Year</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Powders</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Peru</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6864851468449</id>
      <title>5 kg Wholesale Bag (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">167.70</s:price>
      <s:sku>IMP-33014-B5</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6864851206305</id>
    <published>2021-07-23T15:05:48-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-07-23T15:05:48-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-stevia-leaf-powder"/>
    <title>Organic Stevia Leaf Powder (Natural Sweetner)</title>
    <s:type>Powders</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-stevia-leaf-powder-pile.png?v=1626549791"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Powders<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            34.33 - 137.30
            <a href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-stevia-leaf-powder">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic stevia leaf powder is the most natural stevia you can get. Made by simply grinding dried stevia leaves into a powder it can be added to all your recipes to cut down on calories while being more natural than white refined stevia found in grocery stores.</p>
<p><strong>Use <u>1/4 of a teaspoon</u> of stevia leaf powder for every <u>1 tablespoon</u> of sugar.</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is Stevia Leaf Powder?</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Stevia leaf powder comes from leaves of the plant species "Stevia rebaudiana", native to Brazil and Paraguay.</li>
<li>The active compounds are steviol glycosides (mainly stevioside and rebaudioside), which have 30 to 150 times the sweetness of sugar, are heat-stable, pH-stable, and not fermentable. The human body does not metabolize the glycosides in stevia, so it contains zero calories.</li>
<li>Stevia's taste has a slower onset and longer duration than that of sugar, and at high concentrations some of its extracts may have an aftertaste described as licorice-like or bitter.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Stevia vs Stevia Leaf Powder?</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Stevia and stevia leaf powder might sound alike but are not at all the same.</li>
<li>Stevia, the white powder sold as an alternative sweetener is made from refined stevia leaf powder. It is stripped of most of its nutrients and kept only for its sweetening effect.</li>
<li>Stevia leaf powder is simply dried pure stevia leaves ground up into a powder. It tastes sweet like refined stevia but less intense and has a lot more nutrients.</li>
<li>As an example 100g of organic stevia leaf powder can sweeten around 6kg of protein powder. In contrast a 100g of refined stevia sweeten around 40-60kg of protein powder.</li>
</ul>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>1 Year</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Powders</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_India</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Retail</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6864851206305</id>
      <title>1 kg (Vacuum Packed)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">34.33</s:price>
      <s:sku>IMP-31085-R</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6864851206305</id>
      <title>5 kg Wholesale Bag (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">137.30</s:price>
      <s:sku>IMP-31085-B5</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6864850059425</id>
    <published>2021-07-23T08:40:36-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-07-23T08:40:36-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-lucuma-powder"/>
    <title>Organic Lucuma Powder (Natural Sweetener)</title>
    <s:type>Powders</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-lucuma-powder-pile.png?v=1626549821"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Powders<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            153.15
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic lucuma powder is used as a healthier alternative to table sugar and other popular sweeteners. Lucuma powder contains less sugar but more nutrients than table sugar. More specifically, it has about half the carbs and 75% less sugar than the same amount of table sugar. Lucuma powder is low in sugar yet relatively rich in fiber. It also contains smaller amounts of other nutrients, including calcium and iron.</p>
<p>Lucuma is rich in antioxidants, such as carotenoids and polyphenols, which may offer protection against various conditions, including diabetes and heart disease. It is also rich in complex carbs and fiber and may reduce your body’s ability to absorb simple sugars. This may help prevent blood sugar spikes and regulate blood sugar levels, though research in this area is limited.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is lucuma?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The lucuma fruit (also called lucmo or eggfruit) grows on the lucumo tree "Pouteria lucuma", which is native to South America. Known as the "gold of the Incas," the fruit is cultivated in Chile, Ecuador, and Peru. It has soft yellow pulp, a dry texture, and hard green outer shell with an appearance somewhere between an avocado and a mango.</li>
<li>While lucuma fruit is widely available in South America, it can also be found in fresh, frozen, or pulp form in Latin food markets. Elsewhere, lucuma powder (or flour) is mostly only found online of in specialty stores. The powder is made by dehydrating the fruit, then milling it into a fine powder, a process designed to retain the fruit's high nutritional value. It can be used right out of the package and stirred into food and drinks.</li>
</ul>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>1 Year</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Powders</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Peru</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6864850059425</id>
      <title>5 kg Wholesale Bag (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">153.15</s:price>
      <s:sku>IMP-33015-B5</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322909345</id>
    <published>2021-02-06T15:05:34-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-06T15:05:34-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-amber-maple-syrup-quebec"/>
    <title>Organic Maple Syrup (Amber) from Quebec</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-maple-syrup-quebec-amber-pile.png?v=1612639970"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            8.80 - 56.33
            <a href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-amber-maple-syrup-quebec">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>This is fresh Syrup bottled on March 20th 2021. Get some before it's all gone!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Our organic amber maple syrup is made from 100% pure grade A organic maple syrup. Ours comes from l'Érablière Caséal in Milan, QC (Eastern Townships region).</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Why is l'Érablière Caséal syrup so good?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Their 100% organic maple syrup is distinguished by a pronounced maple flavor and hints of vanilla and hazelnut. It ranked in the Top 5 of the best syrups in Quebec in 2014 and received a silver medal in 2015, 2016, 2017, 2018 and 2019 at the ''La Grande Sève'' competition organized by the ''Commanderie de l’érable''.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Who is l'Érablière Caséal?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>After starting the processing of maple products in 1992, the couple Lyne Girard and Richard Rouillard decided to found their own sugar shack in 1997 in the MRC du Granit, in the Eastern Townships region.</li>
<li>Since then, they have been concerned with providing products that respect the environment by conserving biodiversity in the maple grove and by ensuring that regional products are integrated into their processing. In addition, they make sure to choose equipment and cleaning products that meet the highest standards in the industry.</li>
<li>In order to maintain the unique taste of their organic maple syrup, they avoid mixtures, which gives it an authentic taste and allows discerning palates to distinguish the flavors specific to each moment of the production of maple syrup.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What are the different colors of maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>From light to dark the four color/taste profiles are Golden, Amber, Dark and Very Dark.</li>
<li>The darker the syrup, the stronger the maple flavor. For a syrup to make the grade, it must fall within the color range for that grade and have the proper flavor to match. Golden syrup must be light in color and have delicate flavor of maple. In cases where the flavor and color don’t match, the grade goes to the flavor or color that is darkest or strongest. For example, a syrup that has Golden color but a Dark flavor can’t be labeled as Golden, rather it is labeled as the Dark.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What does grade A mean?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>There are 3 grades of maple syrup Grade A, Processing Grade and Substandard.</li>
<li>Grade A quality of maple syrup:
<ul>
<li>Has not more than 68.9 percent solids content by weight (Brix).</li>
<li>Has good uniform color.</li>
<li>Has good flavor and odor, and intensity of flavor (maple taste) normally associated with the color class.</li>
<li>Is free from off flavors and odors considered as damage.</li>
<li>Is free from cloudiness, turbidity, sediment, and is clean.</li>
<li>No deviants for damage shall be allowed in Grade A.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Processing Grade is any maple syrup that does not meet Grade A requirements, but meets the requirement of Processing Grade for use in the manufacturing of other products.
<ul>
<li>Processing Grade maple syrup cannot be packaged in consumer-size containers for retail sales (containers of less than 5 gallons).</li>
<li>May be any color class and any light transmittance; and not more than 68.9 percent solids content by weight (Brix).</li>
<li>May contain off flavors; and odors.</li>
<li>May have a very strong taste.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Substandard is the quality of maple syrup that fails to meet the requirements of<br>Processing Grade maple syrup.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is organic maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You are not alone, while most organic products are pretty easy to understand, organic maple syrup is more complex. There are no GMO maple trees and fertilizing the forest does not sound very practical, so why buy organic?</li>
<li>Some people might argue that all maple syrup is organic and this is just a certification gimmick to raise prices. In reality organic maple syrup standards are more about eco-responsibility and sustainability.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers must ensure the presence of 15% companion species, which means at least 15% of the trees in their woodlot must not be maple. Organic maple syrup producers must also keep maps of all their sites, as well as buffers if they are close to farmland or Christmas tree lots using prohibited materials such as pesticides.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers are not allowed to cut undergrowth, and their fertilizer use is limited to the occasional use of wood ash or lime. Tubing to collect maple syrup must be installed with protectors to avoid damaging maple trees.</li>
<li>There are limitations to the size of maple trees that organic maple syrup producers can tap, the trees must have a diameter larger than 20cm at chest height in order to be tapped.</li>
<li>The only disinfectant allowed, which ensures there are no bacteria in the tap hole when the tree is tapped, for organic maple syrup producers is food grade ethyl alcohol. This alcohol evaporates completely leaving no residue.</li>
<li>Maple syrup producers normally use a reverse osmosis system to process sap before boiling. This cuts down on labor as well as fuel costs. Organic maple syrup producers must ensure that no mineral components of sap are removed during this process. This is generally achieved through the limitation of concentration of the maple sap.</li>
<li>To conclude, organic maple syrup is a sustainable product with strict documentation and inspection regulations. With organic maple syrup you get the maximum nutrients and guarantee maple syrup for generations to come.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/files/Made-In-Canada.jpg" alt="OnlineOrganics Made in Canada"></p>
<p>Made in Canada, buying our organic maple syrup encourages local producers and reduces pollution from long-distance transportation.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>3 Years</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Produit du Quebec</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Canada</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Retail</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322909345</id>
      <title>540 ml Can</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">8.80</s:price>
      <s:sku>CAS-SIROP-A-R</s:sku>
      <s:grams>778</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322909345</id>
      <title>4.32L (8 x 540 ml) Box (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">56.33</s:price>
      <s:sku>CAS-SIROP-A-B4</s:sku>
      <s:grams>6224</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322483361</id>
    <published>2021-02-06T15:05:32-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-06T15:05:32-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-dark-maple-syrup-quebec"/>
    <title>Organic Maple Syrup (Dark) from Quebec</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-maple-syrup-quebec-dark-pile_f4506138-d3f3-44e2-8f75-d359297ebe10.png?v=1612639959"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            8.80 - 56.33
            <a href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-dark-maple-syrup-quebec">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>This is fresh Syrup bottled on March 20th 2021. Get some before it's all gone!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Our organic dark maple syrup is made from 100% pure grade A organic maple syrup. Ours comes from l'Érablière Caséal in Milan, QC (Eastern Townships region).</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Why is l'Érablière Caséal syrup so good?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Their 100% organic maple syrup is distinguished by a pronounced maple flavor and hints of vanilla and hazelnut. It ranked in the Top 5 of the best syrups in Quebec in 2014 and received a silver medal in 2015, 2016, 2017, 2018 and 2019 at the ''La Grande Sève'' competition organized by the ''Commanderie de l’érable''.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Who is l'Érablière Caséal?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>After starting the processing of maple products in 1992, the couple Lyne Girard and Richard Rouillard decided to found their own sugar shack in 1997 in the MRC du Granit, in the Eastern Townships region.</li>
<li>Since then, they have been concerned with providing products that respect the environment by conserving biodiversity in the maple grove and by ensuring that regional products are integrated into their processing. In addition, they make sure to choose equipment and cleaning products that meet the highest standards in the industry.</li>
<li>In order to maintain the unique taste of their organic maple syrup, they avoid mixtures, which gives it an authentic taste and allows discerning palates to distinguish the flavors specific to each moment of the production of maple syrup.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What are the different colors of maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>From light to dark the four color/taste profiles are Golden, Amber, Dark and Very Dark.</li>
<li>The darker the syrup, the stronger the maple flavor. For a syrup to make the grade, it must fall within the color range for that grade and have the proper flavor to match. Golden syrup must be light in color and have delicate flavor of maple. In cases where the flavor and color don’t match, the grade goes to the flavor or color that is darkest or strongest. For example, a syrup that has Golden color but a Dark flavor can’t be labeled as Golden, rather it is labeled as the Dark.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What does grade A mean?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>There are 3 grades of maple syrup Grade A, Processing Grade and Substandard.</li>
<li>Grade A quality of maple syrup:
<ul>
<li>Has not more than 68.9 percent solids content by weight (Brix).</li>
<li>Has good uniform color.</li>
<li>Has good flavor and odor, and intensity of flavor (maple taste) normally associated with the color class.</li>
<li>Is free from off flavors and odors considered as damage.</li>
<li>Is free from cloudiness, turbidity, sediment, and is clean.</li>
<li>No deviants for damage shall be allowed in Grade A.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Processing Grade is any maple syrup that does not meet Grade A requirements, but meets the requirement of Processing Grade for use in the manufacturing of other products.
<ul>
<li>Processing Grade maple syrup cannot be packaged in consumer-size containers for retail sales (containers of less than 5 gallons).</li>
<li>May be any color class and any light transmittance; and not more than 68.9 percent solids content by weight (Brix).</li>
<li>May contain off flavors; and odors.</li>
<li>May have a very strong taste.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Substandard is the quality of maple syrup that fails to meet the requirements of<br>Processing Grade maple syrup.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is organic maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You are not alone, while most organic products are pretty easy to understand, organic maple syrup is more complex. There are no GMO maple trees and fertilizing the forest does not sound very practical, so why buy organic?</li>
<li>Some people might argue that all maple syrup is organic and this is just a certification gimmick to raise prices. In reality organic maple syrup standards are more about eco-responsibility and sustainability.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers must ensure the presence of 15% companion species, which means at least 15% of the trees in their woodlot must not be maple. Organic maple syrup producers must also keep maps of all their sites, as well as buffers if they are close to farmland or Christmas tree lots using prohibited materials such as pesticides.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers are not allowed to cut undergrowth, and their fertilizer use is limited to the occasional use of wood ash or lime. Tubing to collect maple syrup must be installed with protectors to avoid damaging maple trees.</li>
<li>There are limitations to the size of maple trees that organic maple syrup producers can tap, the trees must have a diameter larger than 20cm at chest height in order to be tapped.</li>
<li>The only disinfectant allowed, which ensures there are no bacteria in the tap hole when the tree is tapped, for organic maple syrup producers is food grade ethyl alcohol. This alcohol evaporates completely leaving no residue.</li>
<li>Maple syrup producers normally use a reverse osmosis system to process sap before boiling. This cuts down on labor as well as fuel costs. Organic maple syrup producers must ensure that no mineral components of sap are removed during this process. This is generally achieved through the limitation of concentration of the maple sap.</li>
<li>To conclude, organic maple syrup is a sustainable product with strict documentation and inspection regulations. With organic maple syrup you get the maximum nutrients and guarantee maple syrup for generations to come.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><img alt="OnlineOrganics Made in Canada" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/files/Made-In-Canada.jpg"></p>
<p>Made in Canada, buying our organic maple syrup encourages local producers and reduces pollution from long-distance transportation.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>3 Years</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Produit du Quebec</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Canada</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Retail</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322483361</id>
      <title>540 ml Can</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">8.80</s:price>
      <s:sku>CAS-SIROP-D-R</s:sku>
      <s:grams>778</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322483361</id>
      <title>4.32L (8 x 540 ml) Box (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">56.33</s:price>
      <s:sku>CAS-SIROP-D-B4</s:sku>
      <s:grams>6224</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322712737</id>
    <published>2021-02-06T15:05:18-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-06T15:05:18-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-golden-maple-syrup-quebec"/>
    <title>Organic Maple Syrup (Golden) from Quebec</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-maple-syrup-quebec-golden-pile.png?v=1612639965"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            8.80 - 56.33
            <a href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-golden-maple-syrup-quebec">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>This is fresh Syrup bottled on March 20th 2021. Get some before it's all gone!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Our organic golden maple syrup is made from 100% pure grade A organic maple syrup. Ours comes from l'Érablière Caséal in Milan, QC (Eastern Townships region).</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Why is l'Érablière Caséal syrup so good?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Their 100% organic maple syrup is distinguished by a pronounced maple flavor and hints of vanilla and hazelnut. It ranked in the Top 5 of the best syrups in Quebec in 2014 and received a silver medal in 2015, 2016, 2017, 2018 and 2019 at the ''La Grande Sève'' competition organized by the ''Commanderie de l’érable''.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Who is l'Érablière Caséal?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>After starting the processing of maple products in 1992, the couple Lyne Girard and Richard Rouillard decided to found their own sugar shack in 1997 in the MRC du Granit, in the Eastern Townships region.</li>
<li>Since then, they have been concerned with providing products that respect the environment by conserving biodiversity in the maple grove and by ensuring that regional products are integrated into their processing. In addition, they make sure to choose equipment and cleaning products that meet the highest standards in the industry.</li>
<li>In order to maintain the unique taste of their organic maple syrup, they avoid mixtures, which gives it an authentic taste and allows discerning palates to distinguish the flavors specific to each moment of the production of maple syrup.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What are the different colors of maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>From light to dark the four color/taste profiles are Golden, Amber, Dark and Very Dark.</li>
<li>The darker the syrup, the stronger the maple flavor. For a syrup to make the grade, it must fall within the color range for that grade and have the proper flavor to match. Golden syrup must be light in color and have delicate flavor of maple. In cases where the flavor and color don’t match, the grade goes to the flavor or color that is darkest or strongest. For example, a syrup that has Golden color but a Dark flavor can’t be labeled as Golden, rather it is labeled as the Dark.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What does grade A mean?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>There are 3 grades of maple syrup Grade A, Processing Grade and Substandard.</li>
<li>Grade A quality of maple syrup:
<ul>
<li>Has not more than 68.9 percent solids content by weight (Brix).</li>
<li>Has good uniform color.</li>
<li>Has good flavor and odor, and intensity of flavor (maple taste) normally associated with the color class.</li>
<li>Is free from off flavors and odors considered as damage.</li>
<li>Is free from cloudiness, turbidity, sediment, and is clean.</li>
<li>No deviants for damage shall be allowed in Grade A.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Processing Grade is any maple syrup that does not meet Grade A requirements, but meets the requirement of Processing Grade for use in the manufacturing of other products.
<ul>
<li>Processing Grade maple syrup cannot be packaged in consumer-size containers for retail sales (containers of less than 5 gallons).</li>
<li>May be any color class and any light transmittance; and not more than 68.9 percent solids content by weight (Brix).</li>
<li>May contain off flavors; and odors.</li>
<li>May have a very strong taste.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Substandard is the quality of maple syrup that fails to meet the requirements of<br>Processing Grade maple syrup.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is organic maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You are not alone, while most organic products are pretty easy to understand, organic maple syrup is more complex. There are no GMO maple trees and fertilizing the forest does not sound very practical, so why buy organic?</li>
<li>Some people might argue that all maple syrup is organic and this is just a certification gimmick to raise prices. In reality organic maple syrup standards are more about eco-responsibility and sustainability.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers must ensure the presence of 15% companion species, which means at least 15% of the trees in their woodlot must not be maple. Organic maple syrup producers must also keep maps of all their sites, as well as buffers if they are close to farmland or Christmas tree lots using prohibited materials such as pesticides.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers are not allowed to cut undergrowth, and their fertilizer use is limited to the occasional use of wood ash or lime. Tubing to collect maple syrup must be installed with protectors to avoid damaging maple trees.</li>
<li>There are limitations to the size of maple trees that organic maple syrup producers can tap, the trees must have a diameter larger than 20cm at chest height in order to be tapped.</li>
<li>The only disinfectant allowed, which ensures there are no bacteria in the tap hole when the tree is tapped, for organic maple syrup producers is food grade ethyl alcohol. This alcohol evaporates completely leaving no residue.</li>
<li>Maple syrup producers normally use a reverse osmosis system to process sap before boiling. This cuts down on labor as well as fuel costs. Organic maple syrup producers must ensure that no mineral components of sap are removed during this process. This is generally achieved through the limitation of concentration of the maple sap.</li>
<li>To conclude, organic maple syrup is a sustainable product with strict documentation and inspection regulations. With organic maple syrup you get the maximum nutrients and guarantee maple syrup for generations to come.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/files/Made-In-Canada.jpg" alt="OnlineOrganics Made in Canada"></p>
<p>Made in Canada, buying our organic maple syrup encourages local producers and reduces pollution from long-distance transportation.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>3 Years</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Produit du Quebec</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Canada</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Retail</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322712737</id>
      <title>540 ml Can</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">8.80</s:price>
      <s:sku>CAS-SIROP-G-R</s:sku>
      <s:grams>778</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6062322712737</id>
      <title>4.32L (8 x 540 ml) Box (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">56.33</s:price>
      <s:sku>CAS-SIROP-G-B4</s:sku>
      <s:grams>6224</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314634913</id>
    <published>2021-01-13T11:33:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-13T11:33:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-maple-syrup-dark"/>
    <title>Organic Maple Syrup (Dark) from Quebec</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-maple-syrup-quebec-dark-pile.png?v=1612639876"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            299.52
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic dark maple syrup is made from 100% pure grade A organic maple syrup. Ours comes from l'Érablière Escuminac near Rivière-du-loup in Quebec.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What are the different colors of maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>From light to dark the four color/taste profiles are Golden, Amber, Dark and Very Dark.</li>
<li>The darker the syrup, the stronger the maple flavor. For a syrup to make the grade, it must fall within the color range for that grade and have the proper flavor to match. Golden syrup must be light in color and have delicate flavor of maple. In cases where the flavor and color don’t match, the grade goes to the flavor or color that is darkest or strongest. For example, a syrup that has Golden color but a Dark flavor can’t be labeled as Golden, rather it is labeled as the Dark.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What does grade A mean?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>There are 3 grades of maple syrup Grade A, Processing Grade and Substandard.</li>
<li>Grade A quality of maple syrup:
<ul>
<li>Has not more than 68.9 percent solids content by weight (Brix).</li>
<li>Has good uniform color.</li>
<li>Has good flavor and odor, and intensity of flavor (maple taste) normally associated with the color class.</li>
<li>Is free from off flavors and odors considered as damage.</li>
<li>Is free from cloudiness, turbidity, sediment, and is clean.</li>
<li>No deviants for damage shall be allowed in Grade A.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Processing Grade is any maple syrup that does not meet Grade A requirements, but meets the requirement of Processing Grade for use in the manufacturing of other products.
<ul>
<li>Processing Grade maple syrup cannot be packaged in consumer-size containers for retail sales (containers of less than 5 gallons).</li>
<li>May be any color class and any light transmittance; and not more than 68.9 percent solids content by weight (Brix).</li>
<li>May contain off flavors; and odors.</li>
<li>May have a very strong taste.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Substandard is the quality of maple syrup that fails to meet the requirements of<br>Processing Grade maple syrup.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is organic maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You are not alone, while most organic products are pretty easy to understand, organic maple syrup is more complex. There are no GMO maple trees and fertilizing the forest does not sound very practical, so why buy organic?</li>
<li>Some people might argue that all maple syrup is organic and this is just a certification gimmick to raise prices. In reality organic maple syrup standards are more about eco-responsibility and sustainability.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers must ensure the presence of 15% companion species, which means at least 15% of the trees in their woodlot must not be maple. Organic maple syrup producers must also keep maps of all their sites, as well as buffers if they are close to farmland or Christmas tree lots using prohibited materials such as pesticides.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers are not allowed to cut undergrowth, and their fertilizer use is limited to the occasional use of wood ash or lime. Tubing to collect maple syrup must be installed with protectors to avoid damaging maple trees.</li>
<li>There are limitations to the size of maple trees that organic maple syrup producers can tap, the trees must have a diameter larger than 20cm at chest height in order to be tapped.</li>
<li>The only disinfectant allowed, which ensures there are no bacteria in the tap hole when the tree is tapped, for organic maple syrup producers is food grade ethyl alcohol. This alcohol evaporates completely leaving no residue.</li>
<li>Maple syrup producers normally use a reverse osmosis system to process sap before boiling. This cuts down on labor as well as fuel costs. Organic maple syrup producers must ensure that no mineral components of sap are removed during this process. This is generally achieved through the limitation of concentration of the maple sap.</li>
<li>To conclude, organic maple syrup is a sustainable product with strict documentation and inspection regulations. With organic maple syrup you get the maximum nutrients and guarantee maple syrup for generations to come.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/files/Made-In-Canada.jpg" alt="OnlineOrganics Made in Canada"></p>
<p>Made in Canada, buying our organic maple syrup encourages local producers and reduces pollution from long-distance transportation.</p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>2 Years</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Produit du Quebec</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Canada</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314634913</id>
      <title>16L (4 x 4L) Jugs (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">299.52</s:price>
      <s:sku>FAR-SIROP-08-B16</s:sku>
      <s:grams>16000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314569377</id>
    <published>2021-01-13T11:33:36-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-13T11:33:36-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-brown-rice-syrup-42de"/>
    <title>Organic Brown Rice Syrup (42DE)</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-brown-rice-syrup-42de-pile.png?v=1610555619"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            170.16
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic brown rice syrup 42DE is produced by exposing cooked rice to enzymes that break down starches and turn them into smaller sugars, then filtering out the impurities. The result is a thick, sugary syrup.</p>
<p>Brown rice syrup contains three sugars: maltotriose (52%), maltose (45%), and glucose (3%). However, don’t be fooled by the names. Maltose is just two glucose molecules, while maltotriose is three glucose molecules. Therefore, brown rice syrup acts like 100% glucose inside your body.</p>
<p>Organic brown rice syrup is better than refined sugar because it has no fructose. Although some fructose from fruit is completely fine, large amounts from added sugar may have harmful effects on health.</p>
<p>Evidence suggests that its fructose is especially harmful. Of course, fructose doesn’t raise blood sugar levels nearly as much as glucose. As a result, it is better for people with diabetes. But glucose can be metabolized by every cell in your body, fructose can only be metabolized in significant amounts by your liver. Some scientists hypothesize that excessive fructose intake may be one of the underlying causes of type 2 diabetes. So to conclude, all sugars are better consumed in moderation but our brown rice syrup is a good alternative for people not suffering from diabetes.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What does 42DE mean?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The DE stands for Dextrose Equivalent, which is used to classify glucose syrups.</li>
<li>42DE is a thick syrup with an average sweetness. It is the most common grade.</li>
<li>63DE is a little less common and is less viscous and a little sweeter.</li>
</ul>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>1 Year</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314569377</id>
      <title>60 lb Wholesale Barrel (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">170.16</s:price>
      <s:sku>FAR-BIO1011-B27</s:sku>
      <s:grams>27270</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314438305</id>
    <published>2021-01-13T11:33:33-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-13T11:33:33-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-agave-syrup-nectar"/>
    <title>Organic Agave Syrup (Agave Nectar)</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-agave-syrup-nectar-pile.jpg?v=1610555616"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            231.79
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic agave syrup is a natural sweetening ingredient and is also popular by the name of agave nectar. This syrup is much akin to honey but is less viscous with more of sweetness. Derived from the tequila plant, the nectar can sweeten food and drinks. This alternative sweet syrup can be a food replacement for your sugar consumption.</p>
<p>It is true that consuming agave nectar provides several health benefits. Being sweeter than sugar, the user can consume less, resulting in saving calories. Additionally, agave nectar possesses a low glycemic index, helping users keep their blood sugar levels in check.</p>
<p>It is a good substitute for natural sugar. Do you know that only one third of a cup of agave equal the amount of a cup of sugar intake? As the sweetness content is high in agave you can use less of it.</p>
<p>Agave has fructans and saponins which improve have an anti-inflammatory function in a body. It also gives a boost to the immune system. It contains inulin which is responsible to decrease your appetite, can improve nutrient absorption, and can provide the benefit of added dietary fiber.</p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Mexico</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314438305</id>
      <title>25.5 kg Wholesale Pail (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">231.79</s:price>
      <s:sku>FAR-AG-001A-B25</s:sku>
      <s:grams>25500</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314372769</id>
    <published>2021-01-13T11:33:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-13T11:33:31-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-maple-sugar-granulated"/>
    <title>Organic Maple Sugar (Granulated)</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-maple-sugar-granulated-pile.png?v=1610555613"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            362.10
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic maple sugar is made from 100% pure first quality organic maple syrup. Give a sophisticated touch to all your recipes by replacing white sugar with our maple sugar. Using maple sugar to garnish or decorate your cakes and pastries will give them an incomparable flavor.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is organic maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You are not alone, while most organic products are pretty easy to understand, organic maple syrup is more complex. There are no GMO maple trees and fertilizing the forest does not sound very practical, so what why buy organic?</li>
<li>Some people might argue that all maple syrup is organic and this is just a certification gimmick to raise prices. In reality organic maple syrup standards are more about eco-responsibility and sustainability.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers must ensure the presence of 15% companion species, which means at least 15% of the trees in their woodlot must not be maple. Organic maple syrup producers must also keep maps of all their sites, as well as buffers if they are close to farmland or Christmas tree lots using prohibited materials such as pesticides.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers are not allowed to cut undergrowth, and their fertilizer use is limited to the occasional use of wood ash or lime. Tubing to collect maple syrup must be installed with protectors to avoid damaging maple trees.</li>
<li>There are limitations to the size of maple trees that organic maple syrup producers can tap, the trees must have a diameter larger than 20cm at chest height in order to be tapped.</li>
<li>The only disinfectant allowed, which ensures there are no bacteria in the tap hole when the tree is tapped, for organic maple syrup producers is food grade ethyl alcohol. This alcohol evaporates completely leaving no residue.</li>
<li>Maple syrup producers normally use a reverse osmosis system to process sap before boiling. This cuts down on labor as well as fuel costs. Organic maple syrup producers must ensure that no mineral components of sap are removed during this process. This is generally achieved through the limitation of concentration of the maple sap.</li>
<li>To conclude, organic maple syrup is a sustainable product with strict documentation and inspection regulations. With organic maple syrup you get the maximum nutrients and guarantee maple syrup for generations to come.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/files/Made-In-Canada.jpg" alt="OnlineOrganics Made in Canada"></p>
<p>Made in Canada, buying our organic maple sugar encourages local producers and reduces pollution from long-distance transportation.</p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Category_Powders</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Produit du Quebec</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Canada</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314372769</id>
      <title>15 kg Wholesale Bag (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">362.10</s:price>
      <s:sku>FAR-FLO-1146-B15</s:sku>
      <s:grams>15000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314307233</id>
    <published>2021-01-13T11:33:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-13T11:33:29-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-maple-sugar-flakes"/>
    <title>Organic Maple Sugar (Flakes)</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-maple-sugar-flakes-pile.png?v=1610555611"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            297.50
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic maple sugar flakes are made from 100% pure first quality organic maple syrup. They’re perfect on pancakes, cakes, pastries, yogurt parfaits, ice cream, and many others recipes.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is organic maple syrup?</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>You are not alone, while most organic products are pretty easy to understand, organic maple syrup is more complex. There are no GMO maple trees and fertilizing the forest does not sound very practical, so what why buy organic?</li>
<li>Some people might argue that all maple syrup is organic and this is just a certification gimmick to raise prices. In reality organic maple syrup standards are more about eco-responsibility and sustainability.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers must ensure the presence of 15% companion species, which means at least 15% of the trees in their woodlot must not be maple. Organic maple syrup producers must also keep maps of all their sites, as well as buffers if they are close to farmland or Christmas tree lots using prohibited materials such as pesticides.</li>
<li>Organic maple syrup producers are not allowed to cut undergrowth, and their fertilizer use is limited to the occasional use of wood ash or lime. Tubing to collect maple syrup must be installed with protectors to avoid damaging maple trees.</li>
<li>There are limitations to the size of maple trees that organic maple syrup producers can tap, the trees must have a diameter larger than 20cm at chest height in order to be tapped.</li>
<li>The only disinfectant allowed, which ensures there are no bacteria in the tap hole when the tree is tapped, for organic maple syrup producers is food grade ethyl alcohol. This alcohol evaporates completely leaving no residue.</li>
<li>Maple syrup producers normally use a reverse osmosis system to process sap before boiling. This cuts down on labor as well as fuel costs. Organic maple syrup producers must ensure that no mineral components of sap are removed during this process. This is generally achieved through the limitation of concentration of the maple sap.</li>
<li>To conclude, organic maple syrup is a sustainable product with strict documentation and inspection regulations. With organic maple syrup you get the maximum nutrients and guarantee maple syrup for generations to come.</li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/files/Made-In-Canada.jpg" alt="OnlineOrganics Made in Canada"></p>
<p>Made in Canada, buying our organic maple flakes encourages local producers and reduces pollution from long-distance transportation.</p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Produit du Quebec</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Canada</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314307233</id>
      <title>10 kg Wholesale Bag (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">297.50</s:price>
      <s:sku>FAR-FLO-1135-B10</s:sku>
      <s:grams>10000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314208929</id>
    <published>2021-01-13T11:33:27-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-13T11:33:27-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-date-powder-sugar"/>
    <title>Organic Date Powder Sugar</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-date-powder-sugar-pile.jpg?v=1610555608"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            72.70
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic date powder or date sugar is a sweetener made from dried dates which are ground into a coarse, granular powder. Unlike regular sugar, date powder contains more nutritional benefits.</p>
<p>There are many health benefits of organic date powder. The powder contains potassium, magnesium, and copper, and is a good source of moderate amounts of iron, calcium, phosphorus, niacin, and pyridoxine. In addition, dates are a proven source of antioxidants with strong antioxidant effects. Date powder is high in beta-carotene, lutein, and zeaxanthin. Date powder scored the highest in antioxidant content than any other sugar, even compared to honey and maple syrup.</p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>3 Years</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Powders</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Tunesia</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6011314208929</id>
      <title>5 kg Wholesale Bag (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">72.70</s:price>
      <s:sku>IMP-33019-B5</s:sku>
      <s:grams>5000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6009225216161</id>
    <published>2021-01-12T09:15:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-12T09:15:41-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-date-paste"/>
    <title>Organic Date Paste</title>
    <s:type>Dried Fruit</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-date-paste-pile.png?v=1610460944"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Dried Fruit<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            105.30
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic date paste is a healthy alternative to sugar in recipes, date paste owes everything to the fruit its made from. Date palms grow in desert like conditions, and the hot sun concentrates the fruits natural sugars, creating an intensely sweet, caramelized taste.</p>
<p>The big advantage of using date paste to replace sugar in your recipes is dates add a significant amount of fiber as well as other nutrients. This helps with digestion and well as slowing down the absorption rate of sugar in your bloodstream.</p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>1 Year</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Dried Fruit</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/6009225216161</id>
      <title>10 kg Wholesale Box (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">105.30</s:price>
      <s:sku>FAR-BIO1039-B10</s:sku>
      <s:grams>10000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/5749341946017</id>
    <published>2020-10-03T20:11:28-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-10-03T20:11:28-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-coconut-sugar"/>
    <title>Organic Coconut Sugar</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-coconut-sugar-pile.jpg?v=1603291059"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            214.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic coconut sugar is a natural sugar made from coconut palm sap, which is the sugary circulating fluid of the coconut plant. It is often confused with palm sugar, which is similar but made from a different type of palm tree. Coconut sugar is touted as being more nutritious and lower on the glycemic index than sugar.</p>
<p>Coconut sugar is made in a natural 2-step process. A cut is made on the flower of the coconut palm and the liquid sap is collected into containers. The sap is placed under heat until most of the water has evaporated. The end product is brown and granulated. Its color is similar to that of raw sugar, but the particle size is typically smaller or more variable.</p>
<p>Coconut sugar does retain quite a bit of the nutrients found in the coconut palm. Most notable of these are the minerals iron, zinc, calcium and potassium, along with some short-chain fatty acids like polyphenols and antioxidants. It also contains a fiber called inulin, which may slow glucose absorption and explain why coconut sugar has a lower glycemic index than regular table sugar.</p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>5 Years</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Powders</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Indonesia</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/5749341946017</id>
      <title>25 kg Wholesale Box (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">214.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>GEN-DG1700-B25</s:sku>
      <s:grams>25000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/5749335949473</id>
    <published>2020-10-03T20:09:05-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-10-03T20:09:05-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-cane-sugar"/>
    <title>Organic Cane Sugar</title>
    <s:type>Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:type>
    <s:vendor>OnlineOrganics</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0498/3190/3393/products/organic-cane-sugar-pile.jpg?v=1603291521"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>OnlineOrganics<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>Sugar &amp; Syrups<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            5.72 - 114.50
            <a href="https://onlineorganics.ca/products/organic-cane-sugar">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Our organic cane sugar has the full-bodied taste of sugarcane and is much less processed. Unrefined cane sugar contains 17 amino acids, 11 minerals and 6 vitamins, including antioxidants, that may help reverse oxidative damage.</p>
<p>Organic cane sugar is unrefined sugar minus the cancer-causing and environmentally damaging pesticides present in conventionally-grown sugar cane.</p>
<p>Organic cane sugar is not like brown sugar, which is white sugar with molasses thrown back in. White sugar or table sugar is made by stripping the nutrients and color of the sugar cane plant through a several-step refining process. Think of it as the emaciated offspring of sugar cane. It offers no substantial health benefits because all the wholesome stuff has been thrown out during its production.</p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><strong>Storage Tips:</strong></p>
<ul style="list-style-type: disc;">
<li>Nothing beats vacuum sealing for freshness.</li>
<li>Store below 15°C and &lt; 65% humidity.</li>
<li>Store in the dark as light degrades flavors.</li>
<li>Mason jars make great storage containers.</li>
<li>Can be frozen to prolong shelf life.</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>5 Years</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Category_Sugar &amp; Syrups</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Gluten-Free</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Kosher</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Organic</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Raw</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Certification_Vegan</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Country_Argentina</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Retail</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Format_Wholesale</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/5749335949473</id>
      <title>1 kg (Vacuum Packed)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">5.72</s:price>
      <s:sku>GEN-DG1150-R</s:sku>
      <s:grams>1000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://onlineorganics.ca/products/5749335949473</id>
      <title>25 kg Wholesale Bag (20% OFF)</title>
      <s:price currency="CAD">114.50</s:price>
      <s:sku>GEN-DG1150-B25</s:sku>
      <s:grams>25000</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
